<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[AGCMineral]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[AGCMineral]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 10:28:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AGC Minerals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>AGC Minerals</h1><p>Fine jewelry brand Crow’s Nest illustrates key elements from Walt Disney’s upcoming blockbuster Maleficient with something sparkling! A limited-edition collection of jewelry was created exclusively for the film starring Angelina Jolie and Elle Fanning.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/agc-minerals/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ecbf6d8b-a79e-437b-b17a-c6b9d34508b2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 10:28:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The cost of natural gemstones has kept rising despite lowered expectations in 2014 due to both increased demand and a shortage of supply, especially in higher quality materials.   The increased demand for high quality gemstones has resulted in rising demand for lab reports, which in turn require both additional time and costs. Direct sourcing has become increasingly important to ensure the correct information is gathered concerning each gemstone, which greatly helps to maximise sustainability and profitability, both of which are vital factors for success in the gem and jewellery industry. Not only is a direct source important, but also the right information, which can only be provided through proper gemstone disclosure of any treatments by the supplier. This synergistic approach greatly helps lead to the success of both dealers and their clients.  In 2015, the ICA celebrates their 30th anniversary, after being established in 1985. Great thanks are to be given to all of our founding members and their fundamental belief for an organised and professional gem industry, as well as to all of our members whose businesses carry on with these principles. The ICA’s reputation has been recognised internationally more than ever due to the fact that ethical trade practices have become a new fundamental value of a sustainable business model. The time is right to engrave our history even more deeply into the core of the gemstone sector by leading the global industry of gems and jewellery with proper disclosure, by indicating Common Disclosure Code (CDC) on every sales document produced. From now on, all sales invoices will not be completed with just the ICA logo, but must also exhibit the CDC indication.  On behalf of the Ethical Trade and Disclosure Committee, I sincerely encourage all ICA members to prepare their sales invoices with a CDC column, as seen on the sample presentation.  For our members’ convenience, the CDC list is available on the ICA’s website 24-7 and is also greatly helpful to your clients in order to share both knowledge and understanding as to what exactly they are purchasing.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/the-cost-of-natural-gemstones-has-kept-rising-despite-lowere/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5fbcb260-4cb2-400e-9d58-d685e90d3517</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 10:28:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://www.gemstone.org/images/stories/dragon-ring.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/a6d275da-0822-4fab-a9b5-96af5ef977cb/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a6d275da-0822-4fab-a9b5-96af5ef977cb</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 10:28:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi_webp/JfSgsZ-h1Qg/mqdefault.webp">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/fa9c81d6-bbd6-4dd5-8bcf-b7fba3861ab2/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fa9c81d6-bbd6-4dd5-8bcf-b7fba3861ab2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 09:18:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fe52c94e-1d78-412d-89f3-d9b181436477.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/d9ae68b3-fd31-464f-a53d-a8e8dfa2d589/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d9ae68b3-fd31-464f-a53d-a8e8dfa2d589</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 08:26:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome to ICA - All About Colored Gemstones]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome to ICA - All About Colored Gemstones</h1><p>Gemstone.org - International Colored Gemstone Association</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/be148baf1e114d9767b2a37a4c5ba72ba592800f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.gemstone.org/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">30230fcd-ec18-4e48-bfd8-61b10adbf429</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 08:24:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gondoro La to K2, part 1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Gondoro La to K2, part 1</h1><p>A trek to K2 and Concordia, following the high route over the Gondoro La pass. Part 1 takes us from Hushe over the Gondoro La pass to Concordia.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d2b609c89136c6114dad5684963dcb6a0294043e.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JfSgsZ-h1Qg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a0400c7e-23de-4fac-ba6c-2b867bfc24c0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 08:07:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agcmineral/4762191a-3d70-4de5-a826-00acf7fe0cfc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4762191a-3d70-4de5-a826-00acf7fe0cfc</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 07:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>